谨以此片追忆逝去的童年，如果你也有这样的童年的话欢迎加入我们的贴吧"神剑传奇"。本作品之片源来自互联网，版权归原公司所有。任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途，一切后果由该组织或个人承担！制作者不承担任何法律及连带责任！请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
Stand aside!
让开
I have been
summoned by the Queen
王后陛下召见我
翻译：英语辅导频道
输入/时间轴/压制：harry159821/黑月
You ll regret it
ou-keep her waiting.
地等久了有你们门好果子吃
Enter!
校对：
The moment of trut
has finally arrived!
搞开直相的时终手到了
But this-isn't
going torbe easy
可事并不会那然容易的
But this_iso't
going -to be easy. c
青郑不会那么容易的
The defendants!
被告到
%
No animals
动物禁止入内
Ever since my
return to the kingdom
自从回宫后
I have heard nothing but
conflicting accounts about you!
我就听到对你们的意见各执一词
Therefore, it is my wish to
shed light on the years that passed-
因此我希望了解清楚
during my absence
我不在的这段时间发生了什么事情
Your Majesty
王后陛
Djania are you aware of the crime
you committed by taking Xcalibur
裘娜拿走了神剑你知道自己有罪吗
Yes, and I ask
for your forgiveness
是的请求您的宽恕
I acted solely with justice in mind
我完全是为了维护正义
You will have/ to explain
yourself before the council
亲王会议之前你可以为自己辩
and face judgment
然后
决
shouldnt the princess
put calibur back first?
公主殿是不是应该先交还神剑
呢
∠
第？集
三
Princess Djana
裘娜公主
You are charged with treason
for violating the sacred law
你亵渎了神圣的王法还偷走了神剑
and - stealing Xcalibur
应该以判国罪论处
Tara, you are accused
spying for the Barbarians
塔拉你给蛮族人做间谍也该被判罪
The people of the sea
是海上枭雄
For the". people of thesea
那妙你给海上果雄做间课
and committing rebellious acts
而且还造反
And you, Herik,
are charged with insubordination
至于你哈里克利用法术对抗王室
for having used the powers
of the Shogis against the state
也应该被处以叛乱罪
Princess, tell us how
you managed to steal Xcalibur?
公主殿下告诉大家你如何偷到神剑的吧
Her father stole it
也父亲偷走神剑的
Arthus, please calmo down.
阿瑟斯冷静岛
之
It's the tru
Whenglswent-into the throne room
我赶到大殿的时
fatherawas
Erwann's feet
伊万脚下
驾崩了
lis dead
王陛不驾崩了
王性不驾崩
dead
驾崩了
Fathera no!
Don' t leave
You will answer t
your peers. Ipxrlnce-Erwann
你要给大家
wait, where is Xcalibur? It's gone
等等神剑在哪它不见
You stole it!
是你偷起了神
上公
You stole
是你偷走产
You're a traitor!
你这个叛徒
Arrest Prince Erwann!
逮捕伊万亲王
Take him now
现在抓住他
Erwann fought them off
and escaped with Xcalibur
伊万击退他们带着神剑逃走了
Dry your tears, my child
擦干眼泪孩子
Whoever did this will
be punished, I promise you
我保证凶手一定会得到惩罚
But for now, I would prefer to
spare you these painful memories
可现在我希望可以让你
忘却这些痛苦的记忆
Mussi, please take him out of here.
莫西请带陛下离开这里
How did you end up
with the sword, Djana
表娜你是如何得到神剑
Did Erwann give it to you?
是伊万给你的吗
Nol Erwann obeyed
his king' s last wishes.
不是伊万遵从了德温国王的遗愿
He hid Xcalibur in a safe place:
他把神剑藏在
安全的地方
Fluent dayo liy laher
随间
娜要国三店下聊虎罪前尝
Thate day. my father
and thesking-hadsgone hunting
和我变王前去
Since it was getting late
went to find them
很晚了他们还没回来我就去找他
That's Father's horse!
那是父王的马
竖
Those birds
是些什么鸟
N
Give me Xcalibur. Erwann
把神剑交出来伊万
Youre too late!
你来晚了
Don't be so sure
别那么肯定
ather
父王
That vile Kwodahn
turned my father into stone
那邪恶的科沃达把我父王变成了石赠
D]ana, my child
裘娜我的孩子
You must listen
你得听着
You must be brave/Father?
你必须勇敢点父
he king is dead
and Kwodahn has returned.
国王驾崩而科沃达回来
You must warn
the Great Shogi Master
你得去通知大法师
King Arthus is in danger
阿瑟斯国王陛下有危险
And what will happen to you?
那你会怎样呢
How/can-Lreverse
this horrible spell?
我要如何解除这何怕的咒
Xcalibur is the only way
save me. and the kingdom
有神剑能救我只有它能保卫这个王围
Xcalibur?
神剑
Someone has hidden Xcalibur beneath
something called, the sword tree
人把神剑藏
在一种叫剑树的东西里了
Sword tree
Watrer
Thanks to the Book of Life
多亏有了生命之书
Herik and I-were, able
to get inside the tr
恰里克和我才能进去剑
It's Kwodahn! Hurry, Djana!
科沃达快点裘娜
It was as though
Xcalibur was calling to. me
就好象神剑在召唤我一样
couldn' t resist
and I decided to retrieve it
我不能自已地跳下去把它取回来
Why did you keep the sword
为什么你自己拿着神剑
instead of returning
o the Lord Regent?
而不把它交还给摄政王
wanted to free my father
dreadful Kwodahn curse
我想用它把我父王从科沃达
可怕的咒中解救出来
三
So you used it for
your own personal ends!
那你是为了个大利益使用剑了
Even though× calibur is
meant to serve the community
尽a你知道神剑是用来服务大家
and protect the kingdom!
保卫王国的
Yes, Prince?
亲王你有什么想说
The princess did
not fail in her- duty
公主殿下没有推卸责1
n facto she used Xcalibur
against the forces of evil!
事实上她使用神剑对抗邪恶力量
The defence calls Silkar
its next witness
证人塞尔卡作
This: is getting interesting
Now the game really begins
越来越有趣了游戏现在才真正开始呢
It was seweralmonths ago
是几个月前的事
A horrible(beast was
terrorizing the villagers
有一只怪兽在村子里引起了恐慌
stealing their\.
它不断偷走村民的魂魄
Brian! N
布莱恩不
Don't worry, he's still alive
别担心他还活着
What did the beast do to them?
那只怪售对他们做什么了
He terrorized them
它让他们惊恐
That's how their souls were taken
然后趁机偷走他们的魂魄
but with Xcalibur I can destroy it
不过有了神剑我可以消灭它
Come here! Let's see
if you measure up to Xcalibur
过来啊让大家看看你够不够应付神剑
Come on! I will destroy you!
来吧我会消灭你的
Thanks to Xcalibur
多有了神剑
际动bur
shamans
Princess Diana defeated the beast
裘娜公主消灭了怪兽
and freed our souls
解救了所有魂魄
If the princess tadni't irmervenedo
如果公盒质不平预这代事
the village would
have been doomed
整个村子就完了
d xcalibur
要是我有神剑
would have acted quicker
and saved the harvest, too!
我动作会更快顺便救回所有的庄稼
What?
ve overtaxed the villagers
ma taken every thing from them
你向村民征收过重的收
而走他们所有的粮食
三会
There you have it
你够了没有
三会
re
你够之没有
三
There you have it
你够了没有
Your rebellious
attitude does nothir
你这敌对的态度起不到什么作用
but confirm our suspicions
反而只会坚定我们的怀疑
What do you think, Captain?
你怎么说卫兵队长
Several times we in formed the
accused that she was under arrest
我们多次追捕她
but she refused to come withuS-S
可都遭到她反抗
Give up, Barbarian
投降吧蛮族人
Here. catch!
接住了
Now no more playing around
现在不要再兜来兜去了
s
We were never
able to capture her
我们一直抓不到她
You need practice
们需要多练习下
That was-quite a lesson
for your men, Captain
那对你的人来锐个很好的教训队长
尔
This rebel is just a brute
like the rest of her people
这个造反者跟其他蛮族残暴
This is not how
the king treated us!
艾德温国王陛下可不是对待我们的
You're the one
who should be judged
是那个不遵从他遗愿的人
for not respecting his wishes!
应该被审
exactly vars th含
Exactly what are
you referring to
说的具体是指什会
The king had decided to
give some land to my people.
艾晕鹿王陛下原本准备赠予
我们海枭雄一块地
Erwann and I were the mediators
伊尹万和我在这中间斡旋
and our mission
was almost complete
而且我们几乎就要成功
Tara:go and tell Erwann
塔拉去告诉伊万
that I agree to discuss
this matter with King Edwyn
我同意和艾德温国王陛下商讨这个间题
But you must return quickly.
不过你得快点返回
You /can count on me, Wolf
你就交给我吧沃尔夫
Horsemen!
有马兵
The regent's men
attacked peace emissaries
摄政王的人袭击了和平使者
That is why have
always defended mysel
那就是我自卫的原因
It's a trap
这是个陷
a trap
自阱
Go now! Don't wait for me!
现在赶快离开不要等
Everyone aboard
and man the oars!
全部上船划桨
We'l come back for our revenge
我们会回来报仇的
How can we believe
that Wolf wanted peace
我彻如何确值瑟尔类希到和平
Howg can we belleve
费彻如间的信跃家命凰物平
Howecan we believe
wanted peace?
我们如何确信沃公夫希里秘平呢
Prince Bragan,
lease let her: continue
布刚亲玉请让她继续
And what has become of
the people of the sea,/ Tara?
后来海族遭遇了什么事塔拉
At first, Woifreacted very badly
首先沃派夫详得很激烈
C褊灌猱l
ppM啊
WoUD Jo Ap H
and that Erwann had been petrified
也不知道伊万变成了石
le decided to seek vengeance
by ransacking his castle
所以他决洗劫伊万的城堡以此来报复
anseo sIy.buiyoesupy
aoueebueA Meas /o1 papper aH
He decided to seek vengeance
by ransacking his castle
所以他决定洗劫伊万的城堡以此来报复
But Djana calmed him down
可裘娜让他冷静了下来
she explained to him
mistake he was making
表娜让他明白子自已犯子多去的
buIyeuu SeM ay ayeisiLu B leyan
tuny o) paujejdxe ays
he explained to him
what a mistake he was making
要娜让他明白了自己犯了多大的错
And Wolf finally-understood
that we were on his side
而后沃尔夫终于明白我是同一战线的
Don't forget who
your real enemies are
不要忘了你真正的敌人是谁
may know a way
o satisfy everyone
我有个提议也许可以让大家都满意
Why not ask the people of the sea
为什么不邀请海上一族
You are welcome
to this land. Wolf
欢迎你们的到来沃尔夫
with no strings attached
这里没有任何附加条件
All we ask in return
is to be left in peace
我们只要求大家和平相处
Those are hard terms
for an old raider like me
对于象我这样的武夫来说
是够硬的限制
but the people of the sea accept
不过我们海上枭雄无异议接受
Thanks to the shogis
了法师
my people finally had
a land to call their own
我们海上族终于有了自已的栖息地
And so the Shogis and Barbarians
那么就黑糕师和族人联合来
Ads画^araa
哪畿是师族人联合起桑
And so the"shogis' and Barbarians
那么就是法师和查族火联合起来
formed an alliance
to invade our kingdom
意图入侵我们王国
Is that peace for you?
那就是你所谓的和平吗
Your Majesty
It is now clear
that these three outlaws
现在很清楚了
are behind this treacherous scheme!
这三个逃犯就是叛乱的主谋
Herik, you engineered it a
哈里克你策划了整个叛乱
and used you
powers against the state
利用你的法术对抗整个
Your majesty, this is absurd!
陛下这个说法太荒谬了
The Shogis were persecuted!
法师们都遭到了迫害
We must let
Herik speak for himsel
我们得给机会哈里克让他为自己辩护
Go ahead!
始吧
Your Majesty, all our
monasteries were destroyed
陛下所有三基寺都遭到毁坏
Kwodahn's griffins made
their way into our sanctuaries
科沃达的兽兵闯入了三基寺圣殿
We're under attack!
我们遭到了攻击
不要
Nol
The Shogi Master told me to
escape with the Book of Life
大法师让我带着生命之书离开三基寺
让生命之带酬身你吧嗡重宽
Let the book be your guide, Herik
生命之书引导你吗喻里
The destiny of the
shogis is in your hand
县寺的命运就掌握在你手里了
Bragan destroyed our writings
布拉刚破坏了我们所有资
to eliminate all
traces of our culture
此摧毁三基寺文明
What have they done
他们都做了些什么
The Shogis had to flee
布粒刚在全国备地大追捕三基寺法师
because Bragan was chasing
them all over the kingdom
企图把他们囚禁法来
in order to imprison them
此法师们不得不纷纷逃命
They would all be dead
today if weshadn't freed - them
如果当时我们没有救他们出来
他们可能都已经死了
The Stogie finally took
refuge o a remote island
屙来师们终于费到座孤
倌为难的地
Hkll图m圈d
K凰寞你厮A酃ξ布DT
Herik, this is a strong accusation
哈里克你所说的都针对布拉刚亲王
that you make
against Prince/Bragan
这可是次很严重的控
iCan you prove it?
的哑
c enoId noK ueo
Can you prove it?
你能证明吗
Yes
can. Because it's truel
是的我可以因为这是事实
Prince:Bragan
布拉刚亲
seem to remember the Shogis
were protected by a charter
我好象记得法师是有豁免权保护的吧
What happened?
到底怎么回事
Perhaps we should recess
to call new witnesses
或许我们应该传唤新证
All- in favour say aye
赞成的人请举手
eR
It isn't fair that Mother
won' t let me watch the trial
母后不让我参与审判太不公平了
It's out of my hands. Arthus
局面已经不受我控制了阿瑟斯
Will you still take care of me?
你还是会照顾我吗
We'llsee
我们等着看
Itaall depends on
the result of the- trial
切取决于审判的结果
If Djana wir
如果裘娜赢
I'll have to
leave the kingdom
我就得离开这里
I wonder who their
other-witnesses are
我在想他们还有哪些证人
It makes no difference!
不会产生什么影响
The Queen knows
we're telling the truth
王后陛下知道我们说的是事实
Yes, but will she
let me keep Xcalibur,
没错可她会允许让我拿着神剑
so I can free my father
去救我父王吗
One thing at a time, Djana
个一个来解决裘娜
I-would worry more
about Bragan's reaction
我更担心布拉刚会如何反应
The charges against the - outlaws
are turning against you, my lord
对逃犯的审判转移到你头上了殿下
My dear prince.
you can't change sides mow
亲爱的里德亲王你现在不能改变立场了
You've always
approved of my actions
你向来赞成我的行动
and shared my opinions
还参与意见
It wouldn't turn out well for you
现在的情形对你来说井不是好事啊
f it goes against me
goes against you too
如果是对我不利你也没好果子吃
But, Prince Bragan
可是布拉刚亲王我
Consider yourself lucky
that I'm letting you live
我让你活着你真要觉得自己够幸运
That'll teach that coward
给那个胆小鬼一点教训
This trial is not going as well
as we would have liked, Bragan
这次审判并没有如我们预期的
那样进行布拉刚
The Queen is stubborn and noble
王后很固执而且软硬不吃
Just like your imbecile brother
跟你那愚蠢的兄弟一样
This is what I feared
这正是我所担心的
We have no choice
我们别无选择
Kidnap Arthus right away
and trade him for xcalibur!
马上绑架阿瑟斯用他来交换神剑
You're right.
没错
It's time for everyone to know
about our alliance, Kwodahn
不管对形势有没有帮助
for better or for worse
该是时候让大家知道
我们结盟的事了科沃达
Worse? You
will finally become king
情势更差吗不会
你最终会成为国王的
t doesn' t
matter how you got there
至于你如何当上国王的那不重要
Who's there
Arthus! Arthus!
阿瑟斯是阿瑟斯
Good. Take him to
the place I told you about.
做得好把他带去我说的那个地方
k
Herik. I ould like
to know the truth
哈里克我想知道我不在位期间
about what happened to
the shogis during my absence
法师们到底遭遇了什么事情
Speak freely, you can trust me
你照实说相信我
Thank you, Your Majesty
多谢王后陛下
乡
三
What is Bt?
是什么
N
The shogi Master
Your Majesty, these
young people tave acted wel
陛下年人表现得很不错
If they made mistakes
如郾他们有犯错
They must be forgiVen
their hearts / are p
可他间的小是纯洁的值得原谅
0 implore you Majesty
我求下
Do not punish such good souls
不要惩罚如些善Z的
M
When the truth becomes apparent
实相显的时候
the danger is
closer th
危险也就些想象中离你们变
the danger is
appears suddenly
危同能随时突
The demon Kwodahn has not
finished -making himself heard.
科沃达河没有那么易气就范
He has powerfu alles
有强大的同盟
Be very
vigilant.
I have heard enough
The Shogi Master has
convinced me of your innocence
大法师让我相信你的们是无率的
Oh, Your Majesty.
King Arthus has been kidnapped
噢王后陛下阿瑟斯国王被绑架了
Hand over Xcalibur and
A
g Arthus
release
交出神剑我就会放疗阿瑟斯国
Meet me at the clearing
in the-woods signed. Bragan
在树林里的空地碰面布拉刚留
oM/!-/
后陛下
Your Majesty
Please let me take xcalibur
请让我拿着神剑去救国王陛下
and I will
ing back your son Trusteme
我会把陛下安命带回来的请相信我
accept your offer.
我同你的请求
My son's life is
hands, Djana
我的王就变给你了娜
G
What are we doing here, Uncle?
王叔我们在这里干吗啊
It's a good thing
as there, once again
再一次来到这里是好事啊
Donte worry/
别担心
brought you here
是我带你来这里的
because your life was
in danger from Princess Djana
因为裘娜公主动对你有威胁
Hereis"what were going to do
我们来这就是要对付她
No!/want - to return
to the palace to see my mother
不我要回宫见母后
Kwodahni's there too!
科沃达也到那
We should have known
我们早该知道的
Only youacan fight him, Djana!
有你能对付他裘娜
Tara and I will rescue King Arthus
塔拉和我去救阿悲斯国王
What about me
那我呢
breathe. very large
flames for my size, you know!
我喷出来的火可比我的体积大很多啊
You're right, Wip
With - you on our side
they'd better watch out!
有你在他最好小心点
Yes, but let's not forget
that Arthus safety comes first
不过大家别忘了
阿瑟斯陛下的安全第
Yeah
Attack!
Everything will befine, Arthus
切都会很顺利的阿瑟斯
if you just do what say
只要你照我说的去做
Be off, Bragan
I no longer need you
滚布拉刚我不再需要你
r'm going to take care
of Arthus once and for all
从今以后由我来照顾阿瑟斯
y
Don t be afraid. Arthus
I am your friend
不要害怕阿瑟斯我是你的朋友
We're going to enter
into an alliance, you and
我们结成同盟就你和我
have big plans for you
我为你勾勒了宏伟蓝图
:What is the meaning of this?
你这是什么意思
This is not what
we planned, Kwodahn!
我们之前可不是这么计划的科沃达
Uncle! So it's true
王叔原来是真的
You had an
alliance with this demon!
你和这个恶魔勾结起来了
Listen to me, Arthus
听我说阿瑟斯
will make you the greatest
king this land has ever known
我会让你成为这片土地上最伟大的国王
All you have to do
is give me your soul
你所要做的就是把灵魂交给我
No! Never!
不绝不
Come to my lair.
来我的城堡吧
1, will change your mind
我会让你改变主意的
Traitor! You cannot go
back on your word like this!
叛徒你不能这样食言
ery well!
You asked for it, Bragan
好布拉刚这可是你自找的
Get back, Kwodahn!
回头科沃达
Xcalibur
神剑来了
Traitor! You are at my mercy!
叛徒我真可怜你
Coward
胆小鬼
Curse them! Curse them!
该死他们真该死
Arthus
阿慧斯你还好吧
Thank you, my friends
谢谢我的朋友们
will tell my
mother everything I saw
我会把看到的一切告诉母后
了
It's not serious, he just fainted
没大碍他只是晕过去了
Let,s get him back
我们把他送回宫吧
The Queen must
be worried about him
王后肯定很担心
Poor little guy
可怜的小家伙
Steady. steady!
The monster's gone
镇静点镇静点恶魔已经离开了
You were great, Djana
你真了不起裘娜
Kwodahn won't
be back in a hurry!
时半会科沃达是不会回来了
The important thing
that Arthus is safe and sound
最重要的是阿瑟斯很安全也很健康
When we g
et
back to the palace
回到王宫后
I'll stay with
him until he wakes up
会陪着他直到他醒过来
That's a good idea
ou three should go without me
你个先回宫
because there's something
else still need to d
我还有点事要处理
It,s hard to relax
with you aroun
有你在旁边就很难放轻松威普
I'lI come meet you Djana
回宫交差之后我会去找你的装
after I go to the palace
Where will- you be?
你打算去哪
You'llfind me
near the sword tree
你去剑树附近找我
Father,I have finally cleared
my name of the charges againsremu
父王我终干帮自己洗刷了罪名
之
Now the only thing left
for me to do is to free you
现在我唯一要做的事就是救你出
Now the only thing
现装做的事就是救你线之
Jow the only thing-lefte
Asme - do is to free on
我唯要做的事就是救你咄出
SCKIPT SUPEKYISOK
ETECUTITYE STORY EDITOR
OHH SLIMI
STUDIO MKNEGUK. eLuIrs
PRODUCTIOH KDRIMISTRA%- TOONCEN PRODUCTIONS II INC
LYusIMIYOx Houngoxd
ONI IY SMoUngoxd KOHooI
DINYw taniS
asda
PRODUCTION KDMIMISTRT
3是 ouDe
oDuH从黑GE
STUDio AuEN
LOT
AOR ioDeurooucnons l ime
KRtSTnK rou
HIGE
PRODUCTION KDMINSTRXTOR- TOONCKN PRODUCTION Ill
3D- MODELING
3D-MODELING
6RIBOUILLE
PROTUGTION XECST T
E真R
mixed
分RPHT
BOUTONS
30-M4openrs tresor
VISORs
PRODDToM sTE TAR
IDMO
SUPEKYLSORS
REgno io roehm
DiRecTor O os Geoph
PEKTISORS
器
,
IRTIST
SOFTWARe DETEl
6 IKTIS
SoFT
IMIN TIDA
IKTIS
s
MOTION CAPTURE
SIUCON STUDIO
a
am是wRe
C6C6 INC
Erect
uap器xrso
ASSISTED By
ROUgh8器
SsAO ReSor
OSteO SUn
LKJOUT C UIITION SUPCRTISOY
Dy TSTO
1oc凳鬓 SuPERY
TeCHNNCAL DiReCTO
our a鬓 rIso
recTOSO% PTEGTOR
METWONE IDMI
ToM无
ec"磊egoR
NGTWORL KDI
N基ee
R
Tsas suPERTISOR
NETWORL K
AwoXLTON LU TRATOR
um器是
TS SUPERrIsoR
NE SUPERTISOR
siTERs tsas sureRTsoR
LIGHTING a SPec沿 EFPECTS SUPeRTISOR
在提5
supervIsoR
suPeKTISOR
ut coDlet
翻
TOONCKN PRODUCTIONS XIl
e
sTen Four
I
LE
QuILTY CON
-TORS
dummy
QUTLITY CoN
quay co
TECHNIC
TORS
f iog
ObuCTON KSS1STINT
D(LStSSYRe
onload
部
RECORDING COORDINATOR
PKODUCTTOK ASSISTANT
SISTINT
Assumer ston
PRODCISEO SCQHET TS
KODUCTIOK ISSISTIMT
1NYISESSY MOMncoNd
PRODUC
e
NTKNT3
PRODUC
K CKMKDX-FRKNCE CO- PRODUCTION
e贴
x CxNXDX-FRANCE Co-PRODUCTION
Le cenTre Ti G CTION MOsinee
xC高 HTDA. FRTNCE CO.PR
e cem Ten"器
TELEF
Le cor HTI DET Te
TELETTLN CKNI
ITHE HITIO L
制作
Quebec=孙光辉
Quebe确光辉
Quebec孙光
鬓乐声
Canad
编辑
黄金波
PRoDUCED IN KSSoCImoN请燕
Y
赉任编辑
责任编辑
邓锦绣
吴丽
rmY execuT
ARTISTIc
eDE⊥吧
"器
顾间
顾向
e DE LEno ET sbmemotm华
STEre DE LEMPLO ET DE Lx"裂品m
梁栋华
HINTere De TemPO ET品m梁栋华
从 STere De LEMPLOI ET出tm梨
监制
吴瑞生
ELLiPSANIME
出品人
张新华
Toold孙周
PRODUCTT
张新华
Tood
孙旭阳
T
oo
广东基语传螺有限公司
Y
翻译：英语辅导频道
输入/时间轴/压制：harry159821/黑月
校对：